Pupil's Book, Unit 1, Pages 14 and 15
The First Day
Knock, knock!
It's Lucy at the door.
Hello, Lucy.
Hello, Max.
Lucy and Max are friends.
Today is the first day of school.
It's time to pack your bag.
My bag.
It's in the cupboard.
Where's my pencil?
It's under the chair.
Oh, yes.
Take a pencil to school.
That's the rule.
Where's my pen?
It's on the table.
Oh, yes.
Take a pen to school.
That's the rule.
And where's my ruler?
It's next to your pen.
Oh, yes.
Take a ruler to school.
That's the rule.
Where are my books?
They're on the bookcase.
Oh, yes.
Take your books to school.
That's the rule.
And my crayons?
What are these?
The crayons are on the floor,
under the window.
Hurry up.
It's time to go.
Don't be late for school.
That's the number one rule.