Pupil's Book, Unit 2, pages 26 and 27.
Sarah's Favourite Game
I'm Pablo.
I live with my mum, dad, grandma and grandpa.
Today, my cousin Sarah is here too.
Sarah's got black hair and brown eyes.
Sarah's favourite game is Hide and Seek.
I close my eyes and I count to ten and Sarah hides.
Today, she's hiding in the cupboard in the kitchen.
She's in the cupboard in the kitchen, again.
She always hides.
Oh, she isn't there.
Sarah, I say, where are you?
Is she next to the bookcase?
No, she isn't.
Sarah, I say, where are you?
Is she in the garden?
No, she isn't.
Sarah, I say, where are you?
Mum, dad, grandma and grandpa come to help.
But we can't find Sarah anywhere.
Then, grandma sees Sarah's crayons on the table.
Is she under the table?
She says.
Yes, says mum.
She is.
Hello, Sarah.
Sarah, I say.
Bye-bye.