Pupil's Book, Unit 3, pages 38 and 39.
How Cows Got Their Spots
Cathy is a young white cow.
She lives with her mum on a big farm.
There are horses, sheep and chickens.
There are also lots of flies.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Go away!
Use your tail, says her mum.
But Cathy's tail is very short and the flies are not scared of her.
One day she tells a friend about her problem.
Follow me, says Little Horse and he jumps into some black mud.
Come on! Jump in! He shouts.
When Cathy stands up, her beautiful white coat is very dirty.
Look, the young cows laugh.
Cathy's got big black spots.
Suddenly, lots of flies come from behind the house.
Run, says Cathy's mum.
Hide! Shout the young cows.
When the flies go, lots of the young cows have bites.
Ouch! They cry.
Ouch!
I haven't got any bites, laughs Cathy.
Thank you, Little Horse.
Now lots of white cows have black spots,
so flies don't bite them.
What?!
What?
I'll see you, Little Horse,
I'll see you, Little Horse.
Childish.
I'll see you later.
Come on.
Let me see you later.
I'll see you later on.
Bye-bye.
This is a mystery.
I'll see you later on.