Lesson 55
The Sawyer family
Listen to the tape then answer this question.
When do the children do their homework?
The Sawyers live at 87 King Street.
In the morning, Mr. Sawyer goes to work and the children go to school.
Their father takes them to school every day.
Mrs. Sawyer stays at home every day.
She does the housework.
She always eats her lunch at noon.
In the afternoon, she usually sees her friends.
They often drink tea together.
In the evening, the children come home from school.
They arrive home early.
Mr. Sawyer comes home from work.
He arrives home late.
At night, the children always do their homework.
Then they go to bed.
Mr. Sawyer usually reads his newspaper, but sometimes he and his wife watch television.